<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Music Player NDAB</string>
    <string name="img_view_desc">Image Representing Song</string>
    <string name="audio_btn_desc">Button To Play Song</string>
    <string name="empty_song_title">Song Title Goes Here</string>
    <string name="empty_artist_str">Artist Goes Here</string>
    <string name="song_details_btn_str">Tap Here or Song Title for Details</string>
    <string name="details_empty_str">Details go here</string>

    <!--Song One-->
    <string name="song_one_title">Set Phasers to Retro</string>
    <string name="song_one_artist">Hipster Moon</string>
    <string name="song_one_details">Set Phasers to Retro by Hipster Moon is a commentary
    on the struggles faced by individuals feeling like they were born into the wrong
    time period. It is reflective of their later work using high pitched voices and general
    melancholy. </string>

    <!--Song Two-->
    <string name="song_two_title">Before We Were Cool</string>
    <string name="song_two_artist">Hipster Moon</string>
    <string name="song_two_details">Before We Were Cool by Hipster Moon is a classic
        love song of hipsters who found eachother. Then after finding eachother and their
    relationship becoming too mainstream, problems ensue. It is a lament of the times
    when the relationship itself was as underground as the coffee that the hipsters drink</string>

    <!--Song Three-->
    <string name="song_three_title">Wub Wub Wuuub</string>
    <string name="song_three_artist">Trash Compactor</string>
    <string name="song_three_details">Wub Wub Wuuub by Trash Compactor is a forty minute
    loop of sirens and other sounds of metals being slammed into eachother. A young EDM band
    tries to find footing in the scene.</string>

    <!--Song Four-->
    <string name="song_four_title">Hyper Melt Face</string>
    <string name="song_four_artist">Decipticonipher</string>
    <string name="song_four_details">Hyper Melt Face by Decipticonipher is a trancey remix
        of the classic Hyper Face Melt where the entire song is simply played backwards
        at double speed and triple the bass. Close your eyes and sink into the couch
        with this song.</string>

    <!--Song Five-->
    <string name="song_five_title">Drum Soulo</string>
    <string name="song_five_artist">Drum Solo</string>
    <string name="song_five_details">Drum Soulo by Drum Solo is the self-titled
        magnum opus of Drum Solo. The culmination of a thirty year career in thirty
        different rock and roll bands fueled the fire of this piece.
        Considered to be the auto-biography of all drummers, this five minute
        ear pounder will take you back to you.</string>

</resources>
